unhub.com 2011-10-05

# UnHub

UnHub cares about your privacy and takes it very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the UnHub website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

#### What does this Privacy Policy cover?

This Privacy Policy covers UnHub's treatment of personal information that UnHub gathers when you are on the UnHub website and when you use UnHub services.

This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that UnHub does not own or control, or to individuals that UnHub does not employ or manage. 

#### What personal information about users does UnHub collect?

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with the purpose for which it has been collected or subsequently authorized by you. We collect the following types of information from our users:

Information you provide to us. We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. 

We collect limited information including your email address. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The personal information you provide is used for such purposes as registration. 

Automatic information. We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. UnHub automatically receives and records certain "traffic data" on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, UnHub cookie information, and the page you requested. UnHub uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While UnHub will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

#### What about cookies?

A cookie is a small data file that is sent to your computer when you first visit a website. As with most website cookies, our cookies include an identification number that is unique to the computer you are using. This identifier helps us better understand our user base and how they are using our site and services.

We use cookies for a number of reasons, such as recognizing you when you visit the site, displaying the site according to your chosen user settings and maintaining the security of your account. We may also use the cookies to collect aggregated information about the use of UnHub to maintain, analyze and improve the service.

#### Will UnHub share any of the information it receives?

We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only as described below.

Protection of UnHub and others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of UnHub, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

With your consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to prevent the sharing of this information by opting out.

#### Is information about me secure?

Your UnHub account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer.

#### What choices do I have?

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, but then you may be unable to use certain features on our website, such as managing profile links on your UnHub page.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the "What personal information about users does UnHub collect?" section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

You may request deletion of your UnHub account by sending an email to [privacy@unhub.com](mailto:privacy@unhub.com "privacy@unhub.com"). This removes all of your past UnHub usage from public view.

As explained earlier, the "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if your browser does not accept cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our attractive features.

#### Conditions of use

If you decide to visit UnHub website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of Delaware state law.

If you have any other questions about our privacy policy, shoot an email to [privacy@unhub.com](mailto:privacy@unhub.com "privacy@unhub.com").
